Laojun is Lao K’s official treasure park activity. We already know almost everything about it.
Basically experienced it all. Let me give you a more detailed guide.
The first is how to get this treasure map, right? This is the most important. What about the first way to get it?
This clue is used in this activity, and the treasure map clue is redeemed. The clue was dropped by Treasure Shushu,
Okay? If you exchange it, you can get a box.
Then you can open numbers 1 to 12 to randomly come out. After having the treasure map,
We have to follow the picture to open the treasure. Before I start, I want to tell you something.
Currently, all the treasures that can be found in the boxes are divided into five levels, namely ordinary treasures,
Noble treasures, noble treasures, royal treasures and royal treasures. Among them, the royal family?
It's from treasure map No. 8. High-quality products are produced by ordinary people, while top-quality products are produced secretly.
Then the ordinary treasure chest of the dam will be released from numbers 1 to 7 of the ordinary dam. What about this ordinary box?
The items that come out are the worst, so I suggest that after you get the treasure map, don’t open it in normal mode.
You can leave the secret open, okay?
Then from the 9th to the 12th, you can open high-quality hidden treasures in the dam.
Then from the 9th to the 12th, you can open high-quality products in ordinary dams.
But in the secret, you can get the best. Then numbers 1 to 7 in the secret list are high-quality products.
The ones opened from the 9th to the 12th are the best. Confidential difficulty will all be raised by one level compared to normal difficulty.
So I suggest you just come to us and keep it confidential, okay? Many people say that it is easy to get squatted when opening this box.
So how do you determine whether others will squat on you? It's very simple, just go over there and lie down.
Right? Then lie down for five seconds. If no one hits you, it means no one is squatting, right? After all, people will die if they are beaten.
Not dead means no one is squatting, right? The key is that this thing can be put in the crotch, it will really be squatted.
I just got squatted, what can I do? Gave it to him. Of course, we still need to check, okay?
It’s not easy to collect materials all night long. If you can, please give me a like, thank you all!
Let’s take a look at what these five levels of treasures will yield, and what their explosion rates will be.
This time, the official has written the explosion rate on the detailed page.
But I don’t know why the text used here is “more rewards”.
Then after we know what is in the treasure, we have to open the treasure.
Behind them are a total of twelve dam treasure points.
I have to say that this event planner really knows how to hide boxes!
Ah, are you experienced in hiding private money? Are these places really imaginable to humans?
As for No. 1, it’s easier to find it underground, where the crocodile den was. Next number two,
Under the high platform outside the cement factory, ah, you can see this at a glance. What about the third one?
It's in the middle of the pipe area, which is on top of this shelf. On the 4th, it’s at the back entrance of the visitor center.
That is, this location is easier to find. As for No. 5, the container next to the river beach,
Then there is one hidden here in this small gap. And as for No. 6, it’s on the mountain behind the small military camp.
That is, on top of this box, on the 7th, on the way to the top of the dam, there is a container next to it.
Next to the container. For number 8, go inside this little knot in the container.
What No. 9 said is more abstract. We searched for a long time on the top of the dam, but it turned out that it was not on the top of the dam, but below.
Can you believe it? Come and see with me, there is a small box hidden in this small marsh hole.
This planning is really... Let's look at the tenth one next. The tenth one is directly on the roadside.
Next, I will introduce to you how to obtain the treasure map in the game.
Treasure Shushu has just told everyone, this is considered an outsider acquisition.
Next, let’s talk about the internal affairs, first of all, another official activity – the Magic Container Series.
This time I was given an ammunition box. This time the ammunition box will not only be exchanged for the market series, but
There will also be a treasure map, so don’t miss the ammo box.
We have also prepared a spot with full ammunition boxes for everyone, okay? Just run with us and that's it.
In fact, I believe that Shushu, who is more familiar with dams, doesn’t need me to teach him, right?
Go downstairs from the underground passage on the south side of the cement factory.
There are two in the military camp, both in this red tent.
There is also one here near the pipe spawn point. There is one here at the West Building construction site. There is also one inside the container on the south side.
From the west building, go to this underground staircase. There is one inside the car with the door open on the north side of the east building.
There is one inside a red container in the parking lot. One on the first floor of the main substation.
Ah! There is one opposite the Amiya box in the military camp, one on the second floor of the checkpoint, and one on the terrace on the west side of the visitor center.
You must touch these ammo boxes, because they not only contain treasures, but also instantly redeemable items.
When the instant exchange items first came out, the prices were very expensive, and they were exchanged for some Sijia,
Bullet boxes are also a good choice. So don't forget this. The next step is to airdrop,
Look at the two spaces in the airdrop box. Basically, you have to keep f. But one thing to note,
It’s just that this thing won’t go directly into the warehouse, so after you pick it up, remember to put it in the warehouse.
Be sure to remember it! Next, this is all the points of the airdrop box, and if the airdrop is opened now,
You can also complete the "Animal Work" linkage event.
Moreover, the current explosion rate of airdrop boxes is not bad, so it can be said that it kills multiple birds with one stone.
What follows are some thoughts on this activity! You can really go to normal difficulty.
Then run the ammo boxes and airdrop boxes. The locations of the airdrop boxes are basically around here.
You just need to stand in the middle, hey, pick it up wherever it falls, haha, just squat down after picking it up.
I suggest you use a windbreaker. Go over there and smoke a cigarette, then press F like crazy and that’s it. Okay.
After picking up these treasure maps, don’t open these boxes immediately unless your resurrection point is particularly good.
You can wait in the bureau for ten minutes, or wait for twenty minutes, and estimate the treasure by yourself, okay,
Then open it again, because this box can be opened repeatedly, it does not mean first come, first served.
After you open it, the box still exists. You can think of it as a store.
If you take a redemption card to redeem something, other people can still redeem it.
So don't worry, okay? If someone really squats, let him squat.
After he squats for a while and no one is around, he will leave. You can just drive again, okay? Finally,
For activities like this, try to participate as early as possible. The current explosion rate is really good.
You can take a look at what everyone posted in my first two videos, right? But what is the explosion rate in two days?
I don’t know! So after reading this, hurry up and run!
I also wish everyone can successfully find treasure map No. 8, and then open your favorite Big Red, okay? Oh,
The last point.
The Big Red issued in this event can be traded on the trading bank, and it is very cool to be unbound. Okay,
So that’s it for this episode, thank you all for watching. If possible,
Give us a thumbs up. I will test the explosion rate for everyone in two days. So see you next time, bye.